halfdiscount.co.uk 2014-10-12

# Privacy Policy - HalfDiscount.co.uk

### Privacy Statement

HalfDiscount.co.uk is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site HalfDiscount.co.uk.

### Personal Data

Only a user's email address is collected when users provide registration to HalfDiscount.co.uk. By registering, you agree that HalfDiscount.co.uk may send you periodical emails promoting vouchers and specials from the HalfDiscount.co.uk merchant base that may be of interest to you. Email addresses are never shared or sold to third-party marketers or third-party agencies.

### Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, HalfDiscount.co.uk collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from HalfDiscount.co.uk, our servers log your IP address. 

HalfDiscount.co.uk only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends.

### Use of Cookies

HalfDiscount.co.uk uses cookies for this site. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow HalfDiscount.co.uk to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences.

### Children and Privacy

HalfDiscount.co.uk encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

Individuals under 13  
No information should be submitted to or posted on HalfDiscount.co.uk by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. HalfDiscount.co.uk does not provide any personally identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection.

### Newsletter & Voucher Alert

HalfDiscount.co.uk sends newsletter or voucher alert based on your needs. Newsletter is periodical emails with promoting vouchers from HalfDiscount.co.uk merchant, regularly once a week. Voucher Alert is aperiodically emails with promoting informaitons of merchants or products you subscribed.  
Once successfully registering means you accept our privacy policy. HalfDiscount.co.uk may send you voucher alert and newsletter. Besides, if you want to opt out, just click "Unsubscribe Here" at the bottom of newsletter or voucher alert.

### Links to Other Sites

HalfDiscount.co.uk contains links to sites other than HalfDiscount.co.uk; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as HalfDiscount.co.uk.

### Effect of Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. We may update this privacy policy to this page, and we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices.

### Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy. You can reach us via following address: [support@HalfDiscount.co.uk](mailto:support@HalfDiscount.co.uk)

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.**
